Kristijan Perusko

software engineer

About

Jamaica Estates NY 11432

kristijan.perusko@yahoo.com 111.111.111

Links

Linkedin: kperusko Bitbucket: kperusko Github: kperusko StackOverflow: christian-p

Languages

English, Croatian

Programming

▼ Scala PHP, JavaScript CSS & HTML

Some experience: Python, Java C# (Silverlight), VB.Net Racket, Octave

Db

MongoDB, MySQL

Os

♥ Linux Ubuntu, Debian Fedora, CentOS Windows

Other

RabbitMQ AWS, Heroku, S3, Mercurial, Git, SVN

Interests

I'm passionate about learning and expanding my knowledge. I'm interested in functional programming and distributed systems but I also like machine learning and game programming. I've comfortable taking multiple roles in a team.

Experience

since 2008	Novatec	Software development
2007-2008	Tempo	IT administrator
2006-2007	Vlado elektronika	Quality assurance engineer
2005-2006	Vlado elektronika	Software and electrical engineer

Education

BS of information tehnologyVeleuciliste u Rijeci

Electrical engineeringMate Blazina high school

Certifications

07 2014	M202: MongoDB Advanced Deployment and Operations MongoDB	MongoDB
01 2014	Control of Mobile Robots Georgia Institute of tehnology	Coursera
11 2013	Principles of Reactive Programming École Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne	Coursera
10 2013	Machine Learning Stanford University	Coursera
10 2013	Interactive Programming in Python Rice University	Coursera
10 2013	M101JS MongoDB for Node.js Developers MongoDB	MongoDB
09 2013	Functional Programming Principles in Scala Ecole Polytechnique Federale de Lausanne	Coursera
09 2013	Introduction to Systematic Program The University of British Columbia	Coursera
06 2013	Startup Engineering Stanford University	Coursera